good morning to you
it's the sixty-one day
I'm in this way of the hour bro
because I'm going to São Paulo
is on
and then the guys sent me to a Uber
super good
beauty bro
will fire me
we're not together eh
bro misses no eh
I promise
I promise that I will return
valeu valeu
thank you Digon
is panettone
schoolgirl
thanks huh
Call The Police and The Fireman of Two
hooman remember I was noticed by the Cora bank
now they invited me to come here to São Paulo
at an event on financial management
I'm not silly either bro
I'll take the opportunity I have here
and get management tip
for my business
pô mano
have free juice
free coffee food
I wanted to know if I can make 1 payment link
straight with you
this payment link
the person can pay by credit card
and i don't need to have a machine
for example
or it's not just pix
that's it
take the link and send it on or send it on Instagram
and then I get it straight to my account
it's straight to your account
no problem
if i want to hire a company to do the
will charge ten percent
no need
but it uses now who would say for free right
this is gold
it's just that bro
I was just wondering if that's right
exchanging ideas with Caio here he
Find out about the payment link bro
thank you
tamo together
I'm sure you're wondering
but fell
what was the good
and possibly a business partnership is emerging
mano but let's wait for the scenes of the next chapters
don't believe me
Just watch
from the heart
i feel this stop on you
brother
you're one of the few guys who cares about the message
and not with messenger
is that I'm like a delivery man
just delivering the message
I am delivery man
nobody sometimes knows the's name
is on
because i have to do what others do
for example
I never asked to sign my channel
never asked to click on the join
because I think these things are natural
if you like
from the person what will you do what will follow what will
I never asked
Dude because there's 1 relationship I want to establish
with people
There in business you do something to attract
for people
in a feed where everyone is
my agreement
it's in the middle of all that mess
there will be a person there who will tell the real of the time
brother they will meet you in person
tamo together hand
animal face
animal animal
dust was too much dough man
met the cry I'm a fan
I exchanged ideas about accounting
I understood some things
I'm going to go outside now because I have to edit this video
tamo together
valeu bye bye
obligation hein beauty